reprice.us 2018-03-22

# Privacy « Price Comparison Widget

Last Revised: March 9, 2014

Welcome to the Reprice downloadable browser add-on application or to our website at the address www.Reprice.us (collectively and separately known as «Reprice»), brought to you (the “User», «you») by Reprice Technologies. («we», «us», or the «Company»).

We respect the privacy of our users and are committed to protect the personal information that you share with us in connection with the use of Reprice.  
This Privacy and Cookie Policy (the «Privacy Policy») is intended to describe our practices regarding the information we collect from you when you use Reprice, the manners in which we may use such information, and the options and rights available to you.  
Capitalized terms which are not defined herein, shall have the meaning ascribed to them in our Terms of Use available at www.Reprice.com/terms (the «Terms»), which this Privacy Policy is incorporated thereto by reference.

**Your Consent (PLEASE READ CAREFULLY!)**

BY ACCESSING OR USING REPRICE YOU AGREE TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS SET FORTH IN THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING TO THE COLLECTION AND PROCESSING OF YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION (AS DEFINED BELOW). IF YOU DISAGREE TO ANY TERM PROVIDED HEREIN, PLEASE DO NOT INSTALL, ACCESS, OR USE REPRICE IN ANY MANNER WHATSOEVER, AND PROMPTLY ERASE AND REMOVE REPRICE AND ANY PART THEREOF FROM YOUR SYSTEMS.  
Please note: you are not obligated by law to provide us with any information. You hereby acknowledge and agree that you are providing us with information at your own free will, for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, and that we may retain such information in accordance with this Policy and any applicable laws and regulations.

**Which information we collect on our Users?**

We collect two types of data and information from our Users:  
a. Non-personally identifiable information pertaining to a User, which may be made available or gathered via the User’s use of Reprice (“Non-personal Information”). We are not aware of the identity of the User from which the Non-personal Information was collected. Non-personal Information which is being collected consists of technical information and aggregated usage information, and may contain, among other things, the activity of the User on Reprice, type of operation system, User’s ‘click-stream’ on Reprice’s offers and any e-commerce websites operated by third parties (including Third Party Services, as such term is defined in the Terms), including search queries and related searches on search engines you make, browser type and version, language and keyboard language.  
b. The second type of information is personally identifiable information, namely information that identifies an individual or may with reasonable effort identify an individual, or may be of private or sensitive nature (“Personal Information”).  
Personal Information which is may be gathered consists of the following:  
The User’s IP address or other persistent user identifier, which is allocated to your device by your Internet service provider and used mainly for enhancing the User’s experience and for geolocation personalization and security purposes, as further detailed below;  
Any Personal Information provided voluntarily by the User via Reprice, such as the User’s e-mail address in order to be contacted or any Users interaction with us through Reprice, as may be updated from time to time by us.  
We do not collect any Personal Information from you or related to you without your consent, which is obtained, inter alia, through your active acceptance to the Terms and this Privacy Policy.

**How Do We Collect Information on Our Users?**

We use certain technologies and methods to collect information:  
a. Cookies; a cookie is A ‘cookie’ is a small file containing a string of characters that is sent to your computer when you visit a website. We use cookies to recognize you as a User and so we will be able to provide you with customized Offers. You will need to have cookies enabled in order to use and enjoy our services. We use cookies to collect and correlate certain information about you as detailed in section 10 herein.  
b. Keys and values in the Windows Registry; which include data about your operating system and relevant processes;  
c. Installer Reports; when you install Reprice, the installer generates reports with information about the installation of Reprice on your computer;  
d. Information which you provide us voluntarily; For example, we collect Personal Information which you voluntarily provide when you contact us directly by email for instance.  
We store the Personal Information either independently or through the help of our authorized third-party service providers as detailed below.

**What are the Purposes of the Collection of Information?**

We collect Non-personal and Personal Information in order to provide and operate Reprice and to make Reprice and related services customized as possible to your interests and preferences. We also use the information for statistical and analytics, research and technical support; this enable us to further develop, customize and improve Reprice based on Users’ common preferences and uses and to enable us to provide our Users with a better user experience, with more relevant products, offers and deals and other marketing materials.

**Sharing Information with Third Parties**

We may, and you approve us to share or transfer information, including Personal Information, internally within our group of companies.  
We share Non-Personally Information with third parties, when this is required in order to provide, maintain or improve our services and operation. This is the case with third party offers; we share your Non-Personal Information with third parties for the purpose of providing you with offers we or such third parties think you may be interested in, including based on your statistical Non-Personal Information.  
It is important to note that such third party services may have their own privacy policies and we advise you to read them carefully. Inclusion of a link to third party website or service is not a recommendation of such a website or service. Third party sites may contain information or service that is unreasonable or that some people may find inappropriate or offensive. Before using third party sites and services or before making a purchase, we recommend you to read and understand those sites’, service’ or product’s terms and conditions, warranty, and privacy policies and to ensure you agree to their terms. You acknowledge that we are not responsible for the products, services, or descriptions of those products or services that you receive from third party sites or to the content or privacy practices of those sites, and that this Privacy Policy does not apply to any such third party products and services. You are knowingly and voluntarily assuming all risks of using third party sites to purchase products and services. You agree that we shall have no liability whatsoever with respect to such third party sites and your usage of them.  
We may also share your Personal and Non-Personal Information in special cases if we have a good reason to believe that it is necessary to: (1) comply with law, regulation, subpoena or court order; (2) detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security, violation of our policies or technical issues; (3) enforce the provisions of this Privacy Policy or any other agreements between you and Reprice, including investigation of potential violations thereof; or (4) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Reprice, its partners, its affiliates, users or the public; (5) to respond to claims that any content available on Reprice violates the rights of third-parties; (6) to respond to claims that contact information (e.g. name, e-mail address, etc.) of a third-party has been posted or transmitted without their consent or as a form of harassment; (7) to protect the rights, property, or personal safety of the Company, its Users, or the general public; (8) when the Company or any of its affiliates is undergoing any change in control, including by means of merger, acquisition or purchase of all or substantially all of its assets; (9) to collect, hold and/or manage your Personal Information through the Company’s authorized third party service providers (for example, Amazon Web Services), as reasonable for business purposes, which may be located in a country that does not have the same data protection laws as your jurisdiction; (10) pursuant to your explicit approval prior to the disclosure; or (11) to cooperate with third parties for the purpose of enhancing the User’s experience.

**User Choices**

We value your privacy and control over your personal information, and therefore you may notify us that you wish to either review your Personal Information or delete it. You can notify us by sending an email to: support@Reprice.com and we will make reasonable efforts to delete any such Personal Information pursuant to any applicable privacy laws. Note that unless you instruct us otherwise we may retain your Personal Information for a period of 12 months or a longer period as reasonably and legally required.  
Further, at all times you can choose not to allow us or any third party to collect data about you, or ask to view or edit Personal Information that is stored about you. You may also choose not to accept cookies, including cookies associated with our services or third party services. However, you should take into account that many of the services or portion of them may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.  
If you are a resident of California, United States, or of the European Union, you have the right to send us written request and ask a list of Personal Information categories that we may disclosed to third parties or to which we may give access to third parties, and the details of such third parties. To exercise such right you may contact us at: support@Reprice.com.

**Minors**

To use Reprice you must be over the age of thirteen (13). The Company does not knowingly collect Personal Information from children under the age of thirteen (13) and does not wish to do so. We reserve the right to request proof of age at any stage so that we can verify that minors under the age of thirteen (13) are not using Reprice.

**Security**

We take a great care in implementing and maintaining the security of Reprice and your Personal Information. The Personal Information is hosted on Amazon Web Services which provides advanced security features. The Company employs industry standard procedures and policies to ensure the safety of its Users’ Personal Information, and prevent unauthorized use of any such information. Although we take reasonable steps to safeguard information, we cannot be responsible for the acts of those who gain unauthorized access, and we make no warranty, express, implied or otherwise, that we will prevent such access.  
If you feel that your privacy was treated not in accordance with our Policy, please contact us directly at support@Reprice.com and our privacy officer shall investigate promptly.

**Third Party Software/Service**

While using Reprice we may be using third party software or service, in order to collect and process the information detailed herein. Such software includes without limitation, Google Analytics, which privacy policy is available at http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html; and Amazon Web Services which privacy policy can be found at: http://aws.amazon.com/privacy/.

**Cookies** When you access or use Reprice we use industry-wide technologies such as «cookies» (or similar technologies), which store certain information on your computer («Local Storage») and which will allow us to enable automatic activation of certain features, and make your service experience much more convenient and effortless. The cookies used by Reprice are created per session you launch when the application starts for the first time, and may persist until the application is removed from your computer. We do not include any information about you other than your session and anonymous globally unique identifier key, the date and time at which you have started using the application, information about how you have downloaded Reprice to your computer and information necessary to serve you different content, such as when performing user-interface so-called “A/B tests». These cookies can be removed by using your browser’s cookie/Local Storage cleaning facilities. It is easy to prohibit the Local Storage altogether. Most browsers will allow you to erase cookies from your computer’s hard drive, block acceptance of cookies, or receive a warning before a cookie is stored. However, if you block or erase cookies your online experience may be limited.  
The list below provides additional information regarding the types of cookies we use and their purpose:  
Functionality Cookies: used to identify you as an user and you preferences to provide you with customized offers and deals; we also use such cookies to label you as an opted-out user in case you will choose to opt out of our services;  
Analytics Cookies: used to collect information about how users use Reprice. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve Reprice. Such information is collected in an aggregated form, including the number of Users of Reprice, where Users have access to Reprice from and the webpages they visited.  
For these services we utilize Google Analytics services and you advised to click here http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/privacy/ for an overview of privacy at Google;

**Information Warranty Disclaimer**

Notwithstanding anything else in this Policy, we are not responsible for the accuracy, correctness and security of any of the information we gather, store and disclose to you or to anyone else.

**Changes to the Privacy Policy**

The Company reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and at its sole discretion, so please re-visit this page frequently. We will provide notice of substantial changes of this Privacy Policy on our homepage (www.Reprice.com) and we will notify you via Reprice regarding such changes. Such substantial changes will take effect seven (7) days after such notice was provided on any of the abovementioned methods. Otherwise, all other changes to this Privacy Policy are effective as of the stated “Last Revised” date and your continued use of Reprice after the Last Revised date will constitute acceptance of, and agreement to be bound by, those changes.

**Have any Questions?**

If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, you are welcome to send us an e-mail at: support@reprice.us and we will make an effort to reply within a reasonable timefram
